UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Records 6000/026
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Records
1967-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs
6000/026
10.33 cubic feet
10.3 linear ft.
Records.
6791903
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 25, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/026 AV: UNITE Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs Audio-Visual Materials
Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees.; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Barrett Resources Corporation --Archives; Dixie Yarns --Archives; Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Office of Corporate and Financial Affairs--Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives; United States. Occupational Safety and Health Administration --Archives
6791903
- Baseball: Notes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- FOIAs - Stadium, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Baseball Stadium Property Records, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- FLD Ballfield Article, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cabarrus County Sources, 1983-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Roman County Sources & Checklists (Salisbury) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Fitzgibbons: Personal Property, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fitz's Condo, 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Weclenberg Co. (Charlotte) Checklists + Sources, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Charlotte Public Library, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Salisbury Library, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Library Info, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Individual Profile, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Plant Location & Property Addresses, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Fieldcrest "Guest House", 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Mecklenberg County Real Estate Record, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Lives of the Not-So-Rich & Not-So-Famous, 1971-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Geathers Property, 1973-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bachman Brown Property Records, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ATMI, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Barrett's Resources, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Barrett Resources Corporations, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- KEANE Edgar Proxy, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- D & Bs, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Barrett Resources, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Batex, Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Howes Leather, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Lumber Mutual, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Sesco, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Wayne Brothers, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- NC: Sec't of State, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Wiscasset Mills (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Building Permit Research, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- To Dos + Checklists, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Notes & Info Gathering, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Notes + Info Gathering, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Ben's Work, 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Alabama Industrial Development Training, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- UNITE!, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Scope and Contents
  3 Cassette Tapes
- PTX Contract Comparisons Oct. 9/97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Union Plant Testimonials, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Union Member Video, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bi County Fld. Photos (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Several Photographs
- Letter of Commendation to UNITE from PTX, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- PTX! 98 Manetta Mills - Closing, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Beacon Mfg. Swannanoa, NC, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- PTX '98 Dixie Yarns (Newton, NC), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- OshKosh B'Gosh, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Plan Documents (Clyde), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Non Union Plants, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Rocky Mount (former summergrade), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- UNITE/Firestone, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Dixie Yarns SPD or 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 002, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 501 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 001, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 502, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 506, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Tennessee 001, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Tennessee 001, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Dixie Yarns 003, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Dixie Yarns 010, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 004, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Dixie Yarns 004, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Beacon 502 Wiscasset Insur(Life), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Beacon Wiscasset Mills Life Insur 502, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Pillowtex 501 Medical, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 010, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Dixie Yarns SPD for 501, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Dixie 502, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Dixie 503, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Dixie 504, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Dixie Yarns 005 Defined Benefit, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Dixie 506, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Dixie 507, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Dixie Yarns 508, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Dixie Yarns 511, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Dixie Yarns Material Modifications, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Dixie 502, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Dixie 503, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Dixie 504, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Dixie 506, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Dixie 507, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Beacon SPD + 401(k), 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Pacific Holding 501, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Pacific 55003, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Pacific Holding 502, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Tennessee 001, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Tennessee Woolen, 1993-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- TN Woolens SPD's, etc., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Tennessee Woolen Mills 401(k), 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Beacon Mfg. 001, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Pacific Holding Plan 002, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Atlantic Retirement Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Dixie 508, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Dixie 511, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Dixie 007, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Dixie 008, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Dixie 009, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Dixie 010, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Dixie 011, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Dixie 005, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Dixie 004, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Dixie 003, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Masland Carpets (Dixie), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Tennessee 001, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- D & B Wiscasset, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Pillowtex 501 Medical, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Pillowtex 501 Medical, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Pillowtex 501 Medical, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Pillowtex 502 medical/Hanover, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Pillowtex 502 Hanover medical, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Pillowtex 502 Hanover Medical, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Pillowtex 502 medical/Hanover, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Pillowtex 503 Dental + Vision, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Pillowtex 503 Dental + Vision, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Pillowtex 503 Dental + Vision, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Pillowtex 503 Dental + Vision, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Pillowtex 504, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Pillowtex 504, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Pillowtex 504, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Pillowtex 504, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Pillowtex 505 Cafeteria, 1991-2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Beacon 001, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Pillowtex 505, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Pillowtex 505, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Pillowtex 504, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Pillowtex 503, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Pillowtex 502, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Pillowtex 501, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Beacon 501 - SPD+, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Beacon 503, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Beacon 503, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Manetta SPD - 501, 001 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Manetta 501, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- 5500's Dixie Yarns Mosland Carpets, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Beacon Mftrg 001, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Rowan Co. (Salisbury) Fieldcrest Property, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- 5500's: Dixie Yarns Mosland Carpets, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Cabarrus Co. Property Records, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Public Financing FOTAS, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Fieldcrest Cannon Public Financing, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- FLD Cabarrus CoC, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- FLD Rowan Co. CoC, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- FLD Daily Ind't Index, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- FLD Kannapolis CoC, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Rowan Co. (Salisbury) Richard E. Reece Residence, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Environmental EPA-Air, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Fieldcrest Enviro. Sources, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Fieldcrest - Articles, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- FLD: Fitzgibbons Research/Howes, 1978-1991 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- FLD Howes Leather (Fitzgibbons), 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Fitzgibbons - Probate/Will, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Rockingham Co. Tax Abatement (Pollution Control Equip), 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Mass. Sect of State, 1988-1995 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Carmens Co. Courts, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Hecklenberg Co. (Charlotte) Courts, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Court Records. Rowan Co., 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Guilford Co. - Court Cases, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Ucc Records Rowan Co., 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Meckenlenberg Co. (Charlotte) UCCs, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Politicians, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Political Contributions, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- H & M Contract, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Memos - John Harris, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Photo: Robert Reich w/FLD (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Press List faxed Aug. 13, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Union Logos, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- FLD '97: Company Literature, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- FLD Our News Release + Notes Sept. 10, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- FLD '97 E-List Media (Didn't Do), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- FLD: First Ad - Message, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- UNITE's Leaflets Fall 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- FLD: Eden Closing Articles 10/4/96, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- FLD: Press 2/14/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Desma's Memo on Funding Status of FLD. Bosses' Pension, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- FLD: Capital Expenditures, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Mz's Notes on Holding of Fld. Execs. (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Cabarrus Co. UCCs, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Company Propaganda (Copies), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- 8a3 Reinstatement Clips 4/20/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- FLD: Kick Off Clips 7/8/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- FLD: Kick-off Media 7/8/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Meeting Media July 14 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- FLD: 8a3's: Background, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- FLD 8a3 Press 4/18, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- 8a3 Reinstatements 4/20/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- FLD: Clarification Filing Media 5/27/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Clarification Motion Media 5/27/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Clarification Motion Clips 5/27/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- FLD: Co. Video Media 6/11, 6/12/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- FLD Ind. Trib 6/12/97 'Union Leagues New ULPs", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- ULP Changes Media 6/12/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Classification Denial Clips 6/12/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Media FLD: Clarification Denial 6/13/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Compensation Clips 7/2/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Confession Media July 2, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Cone. Layoff 7/17/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- 7/14 Salisbury + Clips Tribune, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- FLD97: Newspaper Ads 7/15/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Media Articles 7/16, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- FLD: Cable TV Media 7/16/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Media Articles 7/17, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Media Articles 7/21, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- FLD: Vote Demand 7/22/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Media Articles 7/22, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Media Articles 7/23, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Media Articles 7/24, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- News Articles 7/25, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Media Articles 7/26, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Media Articles 7/26, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Nevin News Conf. 7/28/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- News Articles 7/28, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- FLD: 7/29/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Media Articles 7/31, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- FLD: Press Aug/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- FLD: Mass Meeting Media 8/3/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Media Articles 8/3, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Media Articles 8/4, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- FLD: Contempt Motion Media 8/6/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Media Articles 8/6, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Media Articles 8/7, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- FLD: Econ Dev. Corp Hade (Media) 8/8/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Media Articles 8/8, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Media Articles Sat 8/9, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Media Articles Sun 8/10, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Media Articles 8/10, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- FLD: Survey/Briefing Media 8/11/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Media Articles 8/11 Fitzgibbons AD, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Media Articles 8/12, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- FLD: Releases 8/13/97, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Media Articles 8/13, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Media Articles 8/14, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Media Articles 8/15, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Media Articles 8/18, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Media Articles 8/21, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Media Articles 8/22, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- Media Articles 8/25, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- Media Articles 8/28, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Media Article Aug 31/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- FLD Press: Originals Sept. 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- FLD Press Originals Oct. 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- FLD: Press: Originals Nov. 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- FLD Press: Originals Dec. 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Articles November & December 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Newspaper Articles June 1997 - October 1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Releases - Channel 62, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- FLD: Channel 62 8/26/97 Post-Election #1, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- FLD: Pillowtex Takeover, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- FLD: 1st Video - Script, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Inside Packet Materials-Nevin, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Ads, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- FLD: Captures and Responses, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- FLD: Press Clips Bauvelle's, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Channel 62 - Marka's Notes (Box 5, Folder 17)
- FLD97: Channel 62 List of Shows, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- FLD: Objections Media 8/21/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- PO Box (Ch. 62), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- FLD: Cable Votes, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- FLD: Video Production Personnet, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Ch 62 - 7/15 Broadcast Tues. #1, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Channel 62 7/17 Broadcast, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Channel 62: 7/20 Broadcast, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- FLD 97: Ch. 62 Mon. 7/21/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- FLD 97: Ch. 62 Tues. 7/22/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- FLD 97: Ch. 62 Thurs 7/24/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- FLD97: Ch. 62 Sun 7/27/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- FLD: Ch. 62 Mon. 7/28/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- FLD 97: Ch. 62 Tues. 7/29/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Broadcast Thurs 7/31, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- FLD97: Ch. 62 Sun. 8/3/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Broadcast Monday 8/4/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- FLD97: Ch. 62 Tues. 8/5/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- FLD97: Ch. 62 Thurs 8/7/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- FLD: Ch. 62 Sunday 8/10/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- FLD: Multimedia Development, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- FLD: Kunnop/Salis Leased Access, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Cable Programming, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Fieldcrest: Cable & Ad Prep., 1997 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Salisbury Cable contract and Amendment in Aug. 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Radio Spot (Box 5, Folder 43)
- FLD: Exec Pro-union Ad., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Nevin Piece - Background, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- FLD: Cable TU Programming, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Statements (Box 5, Folder 47)
- FLD Company Campaign, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- FLD: Ch. 62 Mon. 8/11/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- FLD97: Ch. 62 Tues 8/12/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Channel 62: Town Meeting 8/10/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- FLD97: Channel 62 Graphic, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- FLD: Media Buy Strategies, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- FLD: Captive Video, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- FLD: Video Productions & Ads, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Time Warner Agreements '98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- First Union Feb. 99 Textile Conference, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Analysts' Reports 1999 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- S+P on Pillowtex, Corp. Aug 1999 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Stock Discussion, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Hansen Property Research, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Court Research, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Court Research 97 Dallas, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Individual Profiles, Dallas 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Property - Company - Dallas 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Property Dallas 97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Dickson - Russell, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Philip Morris 11AM Union Tobacco Lawsuits, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Union Mailing to Workers, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Mailings to Unions, 6.99, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Mailing to FLD ees from Philip Morris ees, Nov. '99, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- NOTES on acq.'s sales, closings, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Sale of Sure - Fit, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Acq. Of Tarboro Spinning Plant (from Dixie) Dec '98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Acq. Of Former Fintex plant Union, SC Nov '98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Closure of Laurel Hill, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Acq. Of Leshner Corp. (and casing opelika), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Sale of NC Finishing, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Closure Cone Salisbury, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Pillowtex: Plants and Plant Closings, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Plant Closing Data: PTX, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Hansen's Letter to worker's, Jan, 8. 98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Old but Good Research Plant list + More, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Rowan County FOIA: May '99, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Cabarrus County FOIA: Nov. 98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 85)
- City of Concord FOIA: May '99, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Modernization FC Contract Language, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Modernization Side Agreements, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Modernization - Leaflets/Testimonials, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- PTX: Modernization UNITE FLD. Grievances, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- PTEX: Side Agreements, 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- PTX: Modernization Grievances Fieldcrest/Eden, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- PTEX '99 Binder Modernization, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- PTX: Modernization KPLS Plants, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Piers 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- PTX 99: Modernization, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 5500's Jenn, 1980-1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- PBGC, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- PTX FLD's Health & Dental Plan info, & Letter from PTX explaining FLD/PTX plans, 1996- 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Kupl Health Plan, May '97, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- FLD Benefit Plan (rec'd 5.99), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- SPD 1999 Fieldcrest Cannon 007 401k Plan (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Pillowtex - Fieldcrest 401k SPD, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- FLD: Textile Fund Pension Calculations, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- PTX: Plant Research/Wage/Benefits, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- FLD: Eden Press + Clips '96, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 1995-1996 Corporate Governance Highlights (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Fieldcrest Cannon Inc. vs. NLRB, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Court Record, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Objection 18 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Decision, Order, and Direction of Second Election, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- 1995 Wage Settlement Media 10/10/95 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- FLD Press: Originals NLRB Decision 9.95, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- FLD Contract Settlements '93 '95 '97, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Fourth Circuit Ruling 9/27/96 Media, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- PTX Newspaper Articles 1987-1996 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- 1995,1996 News Search + Selected Articles on FLD. (Box 6, Folder 32)
- FLD Notes FR. Barg'g, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- FLD: Wage Increase Press 2/19/97 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- PTX/FLD Articles Jan '97 - May '97, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Focus 389 Stories, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- PTX Article Kit 1997 Campaign (Box 6, Folder 37)
- FLD: Our Literature '97, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- FLD: Union Lzaflzt 1997 Election (Box 6, Folder 39)
- FLD 1997: Company Captives + Response Outlines (Box 7, Folder 1)
- FLD: Our Posters/Graphics 1997 Campaign (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Our Literature PTX 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- PTX 99 Company Literature, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Company Literature, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- PTX: Union Literature 99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Press: Originals Jan. '98, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Newspaper Articles January 1998 - February 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- PTX Articles March 1998 - December 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- FLD: Objections Report & Media 4/20/98, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- PTEX NLRB Decision 4/21/98, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- PTEX 5/98 NLRB Charges, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- PTX: NLRB Suppl. Decision and Direction of Third Election 10/30/98, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- FTX Articles 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- PTX Company Press Releases, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- CEO Photos, 1971-1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- List of 5500's and SPD's Current, 1992-1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- PTX Plan 501 SPD provided June '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- PTX Plan 503 SPD provided June '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- PTX "Mystery" SPD's provided June '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- PTX Plan 001 SPD provided June '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Plan 502 SPD provided June '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- PTX Plan 504 SPD provided June '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- PTX - Vedden, Price - Articles DIALOG, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- PTX - Vedden, Price Lexus Nexus run/Citations, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Vetter, Price - Union Elections research, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- PTX - Vedden, Price, Public co's VP Has Interest In, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- PTX - Vedden, Price - PTX's lawyers, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- PTX - Vedden Price Initial Background Packet, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Vedder Price, Distilled for Carmen '99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- FLD/PTX '96 401k and Pension Info., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Podesta, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Fieldcrest Tape #1 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Fieldcrest Tape #2 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Fieldcrest Tape #3 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Fieldcrest Tape #4 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- PITEX Chicago - IBT L. 743, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- IBT/PTX Contract Chicago, Il, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- PTX Tunica UAW Contract Exp. 8/99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- PTX/UAW Contract Tunica, MS Contract Attach. A., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Pillowtex (UNITE) CBA/SSI Torfeaco SPD Health Ins., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Side Agreements Fieldale - L.1708, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- PTX Fieldcrest Cannon Contract 1/6/97 - 1/6/00, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- PTX: UNITE FLD Locks '97-'99, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- PTX '99: Fieldale/Eden Grievances, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- FLD: ULPs/Filed/98/Settled 2/99, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Pillowtex/Fieldcrest Clippings, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Sure Fit, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- FLD NLRB Contempt Petition, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- FLD Money Laundering, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Background, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Outdoor Venture Press, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- FLD Yoru Plant Closing, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Jones, Day - Dialog, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Jones, Day Research, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Jones, Day, Reavid + Pogue, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Jones, Day - Martindale Hubbell, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)